https://craftmoods.com.au/terms-conditions/

Site Information
Loading... Please wait...
Returns Policy
You must contact us within 3 business days of receipt of your order to discuss the reason for a return and organize return approval. We do NOT generally approve the return of an item if you have changed your mind or have made a mistake with your order.
If return approval is given, when the item is received by us in original saleable condition, we will provide a credit for the value of the item only (and not the postage). We are NOT obliged to provide a refund/credit for returned items that are either not received by us or are received by us in a damaged condition. Failure to adequately package a returned item may result in refund/credit being denied and the item being returned to the customer.
We'll only pay the return shipping costs if the return is a result of our error (you received an incorrect, damaged or defective item, etc.) in which case we offer a full refund, replacement or store credit.
Accepted Forms of Payment
We accept Mastercard, Visa and PayPal from all customers. We also accept Direct Deposit, cheque and money order from Australian residents only. As we will not despatch your goods until payment is received, credit card or PayPal payment is recommended if your order is urgent. Orders held for more than 7 days awaiting payment may be cancelled.
Shipping
We only accept orders for delivery within Australia.
All goods are sent through Australia Post. Freight is calculated during checkout and is based on the weight of the items ordered. (Up to 500g packed weight as a large letter $5.50 – not traceable; - over 500g as a parcel from $12.45 - traceable.) All goods are sent unregistered and uninsured, therefore at your risk and we will not be responsible for any loss or damage.  If you require registered post with insurance – please contact us for a quote.
We are currently (October 2019) experiencing problems with the integrated Australia Post postage calculator so pending resolution to this problem please contact us if the system advises it is unable to ship to your address or if you require a service such as express post.
Secure Online Ordering
Our secure shopping system incorporates industry standard data encryption and is protected by the latest in hardware firewall technology. This ensures your private information is kept private throughout the payment process. When you have finished shopping, while viewing the contents of your shopping cart, proceed to the checkout to finalize your order. Here you will be required to enter your name, delivery address, contact details and payment information. You have the choice of creating an account (to save you having to re-enter all your name, address and email details) - good idea for repeat customers - or you may check out as a guest. When completed, you will be provided with a summary of your order which you may print for your records. You will also be sent an order confirmation by email and we will normally process your order as soon as possible (usually within 2 to 3 working days).
Phone Ordering
Australian residents please telephone (07) 53756266 between 8.30am and 5.00pm EST Weekdays (Closed weekends).  We will provide you with a freight quote and you may pay by any of the methods shown above.
Privacy Policy
Craft Moods is committed to providing you with the best possible customer service experience. Craft Moods abides by the Privacy Act 1988 (Crh), which sets out a number of principles concerning the privacy of individuals.
Collection of your personal information
There are many aspects of the site which can be viewed without providing personal information, however, for access to Craft Moods customer support features you are required to submit personally identifiable information. This may include but not limited to a unique username and password, or provide sensitive information in the recovery of your lost password.
Sharing of your personal information
We may occasionally hire other companies to provide services on our behalf, including but not limited to handling customer support enquiries, processing transactions or customer freight shipping. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. Craft Moods takes reasonable steps to ensure that these organisations are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information.
Use of your personal information
For each visitor to reach the site, we expressively collect the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, version and language, operating system, pages viewed while browsing the Site, page access times and referring website address. This collected information is used solely internally for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic, trends and delivering personalized content to you while you are at this Site.
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will use for these new purposes only, data collected from the time of the policy change forward will adhere to our updated practices.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Craft Moods reserves the right to make amendments to this Privacy Policy at any time. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site.
Accessing Your Personal Information
You have a right to access your personal information, subject to exceptions allowed by law. If you would like to do so, please let us know. You may be required to put your request in writing for security reasons. Craft Moods reserves the right to charge a fee for searching for, and providing access to, your information on a per request basis.
Contacting us
Craft Moods welcomes your comments regarding any of these terms and conditions. If you have any questions about these policies and would like further information, please contact us.
Sign up for our newsletter
Name
Email
Quick Links
About Us
Contact Us
Catalogue
Terms & Conditions
